ED
Hello everyone!
Today, I, Mr. Datekatani, have 100 questions for you!
Or is it the other way around?
I'll be doing 100 quality questions!
It's amazing, I'm so nervous when I answer by myself...
I'll do my best!
I'm Date Kaya from Miyagi Prefecture.
I'm in charge of the red color.
And I'm God of the world!
My nickname is Date Kaya, God of the world!
Cry!
Birthday, March 21, 2005, born in Zero5 generation!
I look forward to working with you!
I'm a newborn, stomach!
Bad day in the world, what are you doing?
On a bad world day, I am eating yakiniku!
Bonjiri
I'm a sauce man.
I don't take pictures.
My favorite hairstyle is to let my hair down.
I can eat spicy food like wasabi.
If I dye my hair, I want to do red next time.
I believe in it.
Meat!
What is this?
Cold tofu
The soft one.
Kinoha.
I don't eat much.
A hair dryer is a must for me.
I'll bring my own.
I want to be a vocalist.
What about the skin?
It depends.
Maybe it's good for you.
No, I think I'm eating it.No. Are you eating?
No, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
What's the last dream you had?
Uh, total darkness.
I mean, I didn't dream.
How about summer?
Summer!
Are you a rice person?
What do you like rice?
Uh, uh, milk!
Yes, I am. Milk Ramen
Uh, anywhere door.
What do you like?
I like salmon.
Can you figure it out?
No, to be honest, I haven't thought about it.
I think I like Date Kaya, myself.
Group name, Candy Babies.
I would never do that.
My favorite word is
Mugamuchu
Words that just came to mind
Where would you like to go on a domestic trip
Domestic? Domestic?
Okinawa
Overseas, Guam
I play games.
How many meals a day? It varies, but I eat 2 meals a day.
Favorite animal? I like them all.
I like dogs and reptiles.
Favorite singer and song? Wooo! Well, I like the song "Awake" by Ryubi Miyase.
Favorite English word?
Apple, because it's the first word I learn.
Apple
Do you have a driver's license? I don't have a license, but I would like to get one!
I'll do my best!I'll do my best!
50m sunami? Well, that's the record up to junior high school... 8 seconds...
8 seconds, what's the slowest?
I'm not good at any subject.
I'm shy, but I'm not shy at all.
My boom is a game that I've been playing for a long time now.
Let's play together!
The most important thing is to feel yourself.
As the highest and lowest voice you can make
Ew! Ew!
mmm...
Mmm-hmm.
It's a habit.
Habits.
Uh...
I move.
Is that what you mean?
What do you mean?
My favorite Tochi song is...
Dada Samba.
Because it's fun.
What do you think about during a live performance?
Enjoying myself.
What is your favorite food?
What is your favorite nabe dish?
What is your favorite oden dish?
Who do you admire the most?
Who is your favorite person?
If you could take only one thing with you to a deserted island, what would it be?
Enough food to last a lifetime
Who would you take with you?
To be honest, I wouldn't want to take anyone.
It's too much trouble.
I wouldn't take anyone.
Can you switch with a member?
I don't know.
Who would you switch with? Pearl.If you could swap with any member? Pearl
Pearl.
If you were a man, which member would you want to date?
Not this one.
To be honest, I wouldn't date anyone.
They all seem heavy.
Myself.
No, I'm a pain in the ass, too.
If there's someone you like, please introduce me.
Sports you'd like to play? A sport you'd like to play.
Well, what's a sport?
What is it? What is a sport?
W-w-w-what's a sport?
What's a sport?
I want to try buskin'! I've done it before.
Next, will you be the best dancer in the world? The best singer in the world?
Uh, I don't know.
Hmmm...
Dancing, I guess.
I'm going to be the tallest person I want to be, and I'm not going to be fat my whole life.
Gunny who's never gained weight in his life
I want to eat for the rest of my life
What would you like to say to the naysayers?
It's important to be a follower!
Please be a child
Songs recommended for a chick
Songs recommended to Japanese people
There is a song called "NIWAKA
Please listen to it!
What time do you go to bed and wake up?
I guess this is a day off.
I wake up at 11:00 on my days off.
I go to bed at 4:00 or 3:00. I play video games.
I'm going to get in trouble. I wear clothes and pajamas to bed.
As long as I'm dressed for sleep, I can sleep anywhere, anytime.
If you want to live anywhere, anytime, anywhere. City? No, I'd live in the city.
Gold, if I can buy it from everyone.If I could buy from everyone, I would buy gold.
What's the most expensive purchase you've ever made?
Let's see...
Um...
That would be a video game monitor.
I got it myself.
Partially expensive.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
I don't know.
The most today, um...
Um...
Sadness?
There was a time when we saw each other frequently.
It was a period of sadness.
What's your favorite onigiri?
Um...
I love the belly of a salmon.
What would you like to do in the entertainment industry?
I'd like to do a little acting.
(smiling)
Mmm-hmm.
Do you pick the seeds out of a watermelon first?
I want to pick the part I can see.
What did you believe in when you were little that you can't think of now?
Uh...Santa Claus.
How many questions now...I don't know!
Uh, I think it's about 60, isn't it?
Wow, 68. What were you like when you were little?
Uh, a little shit.
I'm a water boy.
If you could produce a bunch of songs, what would they be?
Stupid songs. I have a lot of songs, but I want to make stupid songs.
Do you have a karaoke box?
Wow, I have a lot of karaoke boxes, but lately I've been listening to Ado's "Readymade. I sing.
The moment when you celebrate New Year's Eve?
Jumping. Definitely jumping. I'm sure all the members will be jumping.
Please give me a screentime.Scrub time please.
I sleep with headphones on and listen to tunes while traveling.
When watching a movie, I always order a melon soda.
But please don't drink too much. It makes me want to go to the bathroom.
I was in the art club, but I only went once. I was scolded for it.
There are a lot of songs that are difficult for Tork-san to play, but basically, the ones that have a chorus are the most difficult. I get caught up in it.
How did you get into show business?
I was approached by someone.
Do you believe in fate?
Yes, I believe in it. I only believe in fate.
Who is your favorite YouTuber?
There is a YouTuber called Inari Gundan.
YouTubers there are very interesting, so please check them out.
What were you addicted to when you were little?
I was addicted to drawing on the wall and getting really pissed off.
Tell us about your favorite thing to do!
My guess is that I recently got blonde hair.
Whatever!
My hobby is playing games.
Do you confess? Do you wait?
No, I've never confessed.
Are you a good swimmer?
Well, I took lessons in elementary school.
So I might drown now.
Where would you like to go with the Inari Corps?
Let's see, Guam. Take me there.
Japanese food? Western food?
Uh-uh.
Can we do without that question?
Well, I'm more of a...
Japanese food.
If you could only eat the same thing for the rest of your life, what would it be?
Yakiniku.
I'd like to eat various parts of meat.
Where would you like to perform live?
Uhm... Yokohama Arena
How would you compare yourself to an animal?How would you compare yourself to an animal?
If you have an animal that looks like a little shit, please let us know.
An animal for each member.
Well, first of all, Rune is a rabbit.
Rine is a Mya Cat.
Yuna is a Mya Cat
Waka is a Mya Cat
Shinchu is a Myakat
Karen is a Myakat
Hinano is a Mya Cat
Miyu is a Hippo
Yes, yes, yes, Myakat
Everyone is a Myakat
Yes, what's your specialty?
I'm an idiot.
I want to talk to him! Kash? Kash?
Mr. Boundy?
I'm not making fun of you.
Part-time job? What is this, a convenience store?
I'd like to do one, just for an hour.
Can I go in for a half hour?
What's your favorite candy?
What is your favorite candy?
Ah! Kataage Potatoes, Kyushu soy sauce flavor.
What's your favorite part?
Everyone...
What do you want everyone to fix?
Well...
No, but...
Um, please don't put strange calls.
Please give a word of love to everyone. Thank you for everything.
I know I'm not like this, but please keep in touch with me.
What is your ultimate goal as a Twak?
Sell, sell, sell, sell, and make so much money that I don't have to work for the rest of my life.
Finally, do you have a word of love for the members of Mr. TWAC?
Thank you for everything. Please keep in touch with me.Thank you for everything. This is me, and I look forward to working with you.
End~!
The end
Thank you very much.
Please take a look at this and get to know me better!
Put it on TikTok!